Raul H. Castro papers, 1903-2007 (bulk 1939-2003)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series 11: Oversized 1903-2007 (bulk 1958-2007)
  - Subject Files; Blueprints, State Capitol Building Reception Room. 1975 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Photographic Material; Photographs, Ambassadorships - Argentina -- General. 1978 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Photographic Material; Photographs, Ambassadorships - Bolivia -- Portraits (Barrientos, Pres. Rene). undated (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Photographic Material; Photographs, Ambassadorships - El Salvador -- President Johnson's Visit. 1968 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Photographic Material; Photographs; Ambassadorships - El Salvador -- President Lyndon Baines Johnson Family (signed). 1968 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Photographic Material; Photographs, Family Photographs - Holy Angel Academy (Steiner, Patricia). 1941 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Photographic Material; Photographs, Family Photographs - Miscellaneous. undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Photographic Material; Photographs, Governorship - Carter/Mondale Inauguration (signed). 1977 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Photographic Material; Photographs, Governorship - General. 1974 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Photographic Material; Photographs, Governorship - Fighter Pilot (Castro, Raul). undated (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Photographic Material; Photographs, Governorship - Portraits (Castro, Raul). undated (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Photographic Material; Photographs, Miscellaneous - General. undated (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Photographic Material; Photographs, Miscellaneous - Horses. undated (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Photographic Material; Photographs, Miscellaneous - USAF Thunderbirds. undated (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous; Drawings, Castro, Raul. 1975 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous; Maps, Arizona. undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous; Maps, Newfoundland and Labrador. 1990 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous; Political Cartoons, Miscellaneous. 1974-1976 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous; Posters, Father Kino. 1977 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous; Posters, "Fiestas Patrias." 1974 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous; Posters, Opportunities. undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous; Posters, Vietnamese Currency. undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous; Prints, Miscellaneous. undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Objects; Painting, Castro, Raul. undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Objects; Plaques, General. 1963 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Objects; Plaques, General. 1966 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Objects; Plaques, General. 1975 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Objects; Plaques, General. 1977 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Objects; Signs, Castro and Zipf Law Office Entrance. undated (Box 30, Folder 6)